If you have any credit card of AAA Bank and
you
get reward points from it, then how to redeem it, I am going to
tell you in this video today.
If you still do not have any credit card of AAA Bank,
then you
can get this Coral credit card,
you can get it very easily, you will find the link
in the description box, you can
definitely go and check it out. Let me quickly
tell you that when you have accumulated reward points, then
how to redeem them, it is a very simple process,
I Bank has an I mobile application,
you have to log in to it,
simply you will find all your credit cards of
ICICI Bank here,
in the entire video
you will see some things blurred due to
security reasons, simply
you have to go to the section of my cards, here you will see
two of my cards, some things will be blurred,
so you have to tap on the card for which
you want to redeem the reward points,
after tapping on it, it will show you how many reward points you have here, brother.  You
can check here if it is available with you, in my case I have
3136 reward points available here. Now to
redeem these reward points,
you simply have to tap on the redeem button.
When you go here, you will
see many products, you will also see many gift
vouchers. If you
look here, you will see many products etc.
Okay, you can
shop some of the things that you want to shop,
but according to me, it is better to take a voucher
because
if you
go for a gift voucher like this chopper, then
you will have to have a minimum of 5000 or 3000 or 2000, so
if I want to
take a gift voucher of 3000, then I should have minimum reward
points here, 12000, that is, the
value of one reward point is 0.25
paisa, but I am not going to take this here.
I want a Prime
membership voucher here, so here  But you
click on search and after going to search,
search for Prime. If you
search for Prime, you will see 3 months, 6 months
or 12 months. I
want three months. Simply, you have to click on this.
As soon as you click here,
you will see this voucher.
Simply, those
2396 reward points will be debited
and I will be able to see this voucher.
Simply, you have to click on the add cart button.
You have to click on the go cart button. If you
see here, then my
reward points will be reduced here.
Click on the proceed to checkout button. My name has come, my
email address on which they will provide me a unique
code and this is my mobile
number. Simply, I clicked on the proceed to redeem button here.
After doing this, an OTP will come on my number.
Simply, I have received the OTP.
I submitted the OTP here.
After doing this, it will be written here that it has come.
Congratulations, my name has come
within 30 minutes
on my registered mail ID, which is here, I will send it to you.